Hi everyone, emotional agility is such a crucial skill set, especially in our complex changing world.
When we come to our lives with emotional agility, we are able to cultivate the skills that we need
so that we can love and lead and parent more effectively. Here are four key capacities of emotional
agility. The first is compassion. It's hard to human. Give yourself grace and love and dignity
when you are suffering. Number two is courage. It takes courage to move to hard things. It takes
courage to walk in your values and it takes courage to experience tough emotions. Recognize that courage
isn't always loud. Sometimes courage is a whisper. It's the reassurance and it's the love
that you give to yourself. Number three is curiosity. When we are curious in the world,
when we are open to growth and learning, we expand our capacity. And one way of being curious
is external. Another way of being curious is internal. See when you experience difficult emotions
if you can recognize what those emotions are signposting. We might, for example,
when we feel lonely, see only the lonely. And yet the lonely is often signaling that we need more
connection and intimacy in our lives. It's a beautiful invitation to walk more towards that thing.
And last is centeredness. When the world is changing around us, we need to be grounded in ourselves.
It doesn't mean that you always have the answer or always know the path, but you always know that you
will come back to you.